[Music]
yeah so you just graduated all those
years of hard work have finally paid off
what's next higher studies or a
rewarding career in banking what if you
can have both in one goal ICICI Bank in
partnership with moneal global Education
Services private limited gives you an
opportunity to pursue a one-year
full-time program to become a
probationary officer at ICI bank and the
highlight of the course internship and
on the- job training with stipend a
post-graduate diploma in
banking a rewarding career in sales and
relationship management and an
opportunity to serve
customers sounds like a plan if you are
a graduate in any discipline and love
handling sales and customer
relationships this is your ticket to an
amazing career Journey so if you want to
be a banker and make use of a unique
opportunity to serve customers this is
the best opportunity ever apply now for
a brighter future